snowboard-asylum.com 2017-07-08

# Privacy & Cookie Policy - The Snowboard Asylum

## Privacy Policy

The Snowboard Asylum is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

## What we collect and Why

In order to process orders and send out newsletters, we will request your personal details, such as name, address, email address, telephone number. We do not collect debit or credit card information. For all online purchases this information is entered through a secure payment gateway provided by our online banking partners, and we do not have access to the data. To find out more about the banking partners we use, please email us at [customer.services@snowboard-asylum.com](mailto:customer.services@snowboard-asylum.com)

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at [customer.services@snowboard-asylum.com](mailto:customer.services@snowboard-asylum.com)
  * We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us at[ customer.services@snowboard-asylum.com](mailto:customer.services@snowboard-asylum.com). If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

We can greatly improve your experience of our website by knowing your preferences. Allowing us to customise the Website according to your individual interests means we can offer a great personalised service. To help us remember these preferences we use a small text file, often referred to as a ‘cookie’, which we will place on each computer you use to access our site.

Cookies allow us to recognise your preferences as previously chosen by you when you return to our site. The cookie itself does not contain or collect personally identifiable information. However, when it is read by us it can help our web team deliver a more user-friendly experience – for example, remembering previous purchases, account details and helping us recommend products that suit you and your lifestyle!

When we send you a cookie only our web server can read them; information gathered by us never goes outside our control and is not shared with other organisations for their marketing purposes. Information obtained via cookies may be processed by our partners who are controlled under contract and required to comply with the Data Protection Act 1998.

Informed Choice: It is your decision whether to accept or consent to cookies or not. If you do not consent to them you can adjust the settings of you browser software to either delete cookies which already exist and/or block new ones from being stored or accessed. Many browsers now provide specific ‘add-ons’ to help you manage your privacy online. See www.aboutcookies.org for more help and advice.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website (with the exception of [www.snowboard-asylum.com](http://www.snowboard-asylum.com/)). Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
